Greetings.  Today is 15th August.  Let me
show you
how 15th August is being celebrated in our building.  Look,
everything is decorated here.
People from our society have also come.  The flag is being hoisted here.
We also came here and got our
photographs taken and
consider this as our first 15th August here.  We also drank tea here.
Well, it's good that I got tea.  He had
not come home drunk.  Children are playing games here and
they got gifts.  Saif had gone home.
Then he came and closed my eyes and
scared me.  Saif is getting his number added to the society group.  If
any program takes place in the building,
we should also get the message.
Look, everyone is getting breakfast here.
Everyone, young and old, got it.  We brought it home
and gave everyone a packet of breakfast.  The whole
family has got it.  We are all sitting and eating.